Any luck?
Check Interpol and the
Sardinian police records.
Can you find any matching
sets of fingerprints?
I'm sorry, but nothing's coming up.
If there ever was a criminal record,
I'm sure the boss has had
it completely wiped by now.
Damn it.
I'm certain there must be something.
Or else this makes no sense.
If his identity weren't at risk, why
else would he target his own daughter?
Why don't we go look through
the city death records?
There's a possibility the boss
might have faked his own death.
Give it a shot.
We can't let him get away.
For a moment, that feeling
came over me again.
Just like in Venice.
The person who approached
Abacchio was my father.
I know he murdered Abacchio
using us on two hands.
Do you mean to say you can
sense his presence right now?
Yes.
I can't tell you where exactly,
but he's nearby. Bucciarati!
There's no time.
Should we fail to identify
and dispatch the boss in time,
it will be our ugly heads that roll.
Ascolta!
We have to locate him fast!
Huh?
Still no matches.
It's no use.
He's covered his tracks expertly.
Miseria.
Seems we've hit a dead end.
I wouldn't say that.
You've already succeeded in
finding your court. Wait, what?
You need only learn
the way to destroy him.
And start
What's that? To you?
To you?
Thank you
so
much for watching.
I've been waiting for so long,
so long for ones like you to hunt
down this vile, this Despicable man!
Jonah, we're being tracked!
Quickly, cut the communication!
Wait!
Don't do that!
I'm trying to help you!
Don't you wish to defeat Diablo?
Diablo?
Please, believe me.
I've always had hope that a hero with the
strength to slay Diablo
would one day appear.
That's why I've kept a
close watch on this line.
So many arduous years of doubt and anxiety
I braved, all in wait of your arrival.
I am on your side.
Diavolo, you say?
Forgive my weariness,
but it will take a whole
lot more than simply
knowing a name to convince
me you're trustworthy.
Giorno, please disconnect us.
I also know his stand has the
power to travel through time.
But you knew that as well.
Which, I would dare to wager,
is exactly why you're scrambling to
uncover this man's true identity.
He is on our side.
He's trying to help us.
No underling of my father could
know all this and still be alive!
Hold on a sec, Trish.
We really don't want to risk
showing our hand too soon.
Fine, we'll hear you out.
Please start by telling us your name.
That's not something you need to know.
I'm no longer in any physical
condition to engage in combat.
All that matters is whether you
are able to beat this monster.
His ability to distort time
itself has no weakness, Yes.
As things stand,
if your ultimate goal is to eliminate him
for good, then you are doomed to fail.
I'm assuming that you know the secret
to defeating him once and for all?
Emperor Crimson is virtually invincible.
But yes, there is a way you might
still stand a chance, a slim one.
And you will have no other
choice but to obtain it.
What exactly do you mean?
You must come meet me
here, in the city of Rome.
Only then will I be able to
show you the path to victory.
Are you really demanding
personal visits already?
We've only just met.
I'm certain at least some of
you are familiar with this item.
No way!
That's the arrow!
I mean, it looks like it.
How did it come to be in your possession?
I'll gladly share this story,
but only once you've come to
retrieve it and not a second before.
Not even he knows the
true way to use the arrow.
Its powers extend beyond simply
awakening one's standard ability.
It bears a hidden wisdom
which I shall teach you.
You must come to Rome.
The arrow holds the key to his defeat.
It's the only way you can hope to prevail.
Hey, you there!
The hell do you get
off answering my phone?
That calls for me, damn it!
Give me that, you stupid brat!
Yes?
Hello, it's Deep speaking.
It's strange, Deep.
What do you mean, boss?
Bucciarati's crew. Yeah.
One would imagine the loss of a dear
comrade might addle their composures.
Yet oddly, not a trace of
hesitation haunts them.
They have now boarded a boat
with a clear goal in their minds.
Investigate, return to Abakyo's
last location, and look around.
Something is off.
I can do that, but what
am I supposed to look for?
Fear is what arises from the
womb of an unexpected past.
Ever since I learned of my daughter,
I have felt a sense of disquiet.
I'm not seeing anything
out of the ordinary, boss.
All they did was break the monument.
I know.
I can feel it.
I know what they've done.
Those traitors.
They've found information I don't possess.
But how can that be?
No way they could have learned
anything useful in such a rush.
This is unimaginable.
Listen, Dobio.
We must make our move now.
I urgently need you to
track them down yourself.
Got it!
Also, have Cioccolata and Seko
come join the pursuit as well.
I would have preferred not
to rely on those dregs.
But alas, we won't need them again.
Listen, Dobio.
The only way to deal with
fear is to crush it into dust.
It is time for us to act.
We must triumph over our
fears once and for all.
That is what it means to be truly alive.
Who the hell are we going all the
way to frickin' Rome for anyway?
I mean, can we even trust this guy?
Beats me.
But Bucciarati said we're
going, so we're going.
What other choice do we have?
Let me share with you a
little piece of history.
In Greenland lies a place called Cape
York, inhabited solely by the Inuit people.
It's known for being home to
a massive meteorite crater,
which came into being
thousands of years ago.
Then, in 1978,
while a team of surveyors were conducting
a land resource survey of the crater,
two of them were stricken
by a strange illness.
In both cases,
blisters began spreading
all over their bodies,
breaking them down into unrecognizable
pulps upon their deaths.
But in one of those cases,
the afflicted surveyor discharged a
bizarre spark of light from his fingertips,
maiming several digits
on his doctor's hand.
Subsequent investigations
revealed that a mysterious virus,
one many thousands of years old,
had resided within the meteorite.
Scientists believe the two may have
come into contact somewhere in space.
So there's a virus.
What of it?
I've successfully tracked it down.
The arrow is made from the same material
as the meteorite from Cape York.
Centuries ago,
a man who sought the
power of the gods learned
of this rock and used
it to create the arrows,
one of which I have in my possession.
The behavior of this killer
virus mimics natural selection,
in that it propagates a
type of viral evolution.
Most who contract the
virus do not survive,
but the few that do seem to be
protected by a specific trait.
And as if to reward this trait,
the virus bestows upon its
host a new biological ability.
I'm certain you need no evidence, as
your bodies already know this to be true.
so that's what stands are this is the root
and the fundamental principle of the arrow
i see that now your
explanations sound but you
have yet to tell us
about this secret method
of using the arrow why
we must come to retrieve
it from you i cannot
reveal that to you until
you've come to meet me
in rome and i should
clarify only one of you
may learn this secret
because it is imperative
that no one else ever
comes to know of the true
power this arrow holds.
But rest assured,
whoever learns the truth of this item will
be instantly transported
to a new dimension.
It is the only way you can hope
to destroy Emperor Crimson.
We cannot affirm the truth of your words.
However, if the boss learned of our
exchange, he would surely end your life.
I shall trust you.
Name your rendezvous point.
Come to the Colosseum in Rome.
You'll know when you arrive.
I'll be there regardless of the time.
Soon, all will be revealed.
Hey, come on!
Get your ass off of there, you idiot!
Leave me alone!
I'm about to piss myself!
Like hell, you're gonna let go already!
This ain't the crapper!
It's over here, you shithead!
What a feeling!
I'm-a do it!
Let's wait till those
drunks leave and then duck.
Right after which, we should obtain a car.
That should put us under
45 minutes out of Rome.
Aye aye, Captain.
Captain, I'm sure that
we'll make real good time.
Clouds are obscuring the moon, too.
Yo, Mista!
There's a couple of them
napping right over there!
Shit!
These guys cannot hold their liquor!
Come on, you're gonna get us in trouble!
Let me go!
I said I'm gonna do it,
and I'm gonna do it!
I told you there ain't no toilet.
Look, it's over here.
Hey.
The problem is I can't reach my Papa now.
Because I'm all the way up here, and it's
way down there trapped inside my zipper.
What the hell is going on here?
Don't touch me!
What just happened to him?
It looks like there's a
stand on the loose. A stand?
Yeah, it's a freaking ambush.
Watch out!
Now then, Seko.
Remember to keep a close
eye on that battery level.
It's very important to my work.
You know nothing irks
me more than finding out
the damn thing wasn't
recording after the fact,
so make sure it is.
Good boy.
Cioccolata, 34 years
old, former physician.
Two years ago, after a minor error
had seemingly killed a patient,
he was let go from the hospital
and picked up by Passione.
He had suffered a
humiliating fall from grace,
but the boss soon realized Chocolata's value
when the young doctor acquired a stand.
It was not a mistake that had killed the
patient, but Chocolata's murderous motives.
He would purposely misdiagnose healthy
individuals to get them
on his operating table.
Part of his routine
involved reducing their
anesthesia so they would
wake up during surgery.
Even as a child, he was
at the top of his class.
At the age of 14, he decided to
begin volunteering at nursing homes.
Little did people know, however?
The teenager was administering unknown
drugs to his elderly charges and also
Your family tells me you're nothing but a
burden and they can't
stand the sight of you
Each day he'd whisper venomous lies
Driving those in his care to suicide
sitting on his bookshelf at home were
25 tapes in which he had documented the
horrified expressions of his victims.
Once he had claimed nine lives,
Cioccolata decided to become a doctor.
No activity brought him more ecstasy
than observing death in action.
And being a physician allowed him
to watch the dying suffer up close.
To see his victims decay in such vivid
detail filled him with a sense of
superiority and made him feel as though
he truly understood the mind of man.
Chocolata's sole partner in
his depravities was Seko.
Little is known of him beyond the fact
that he was once Chocolata's patient.
Their chemistry led to an arrangement
where Seko only follows Chocolata's orders.
And even among Pasione's many
vile-hearted stand-users,
the wickedness of this
particular duo stands out.
So goes the story of Cioccolata and Seko.
It's looking to me like they're currently
making their way toward Rome, boss.
I just received word
that they've arrived at
a fishing village pretty
close to the city.
Listen, Deep.
The task of stopping Bucciarati and his
men will be left to Cioccolata and his dog.
But afterwards, it will be up to you to
catch up to them as soon as possible.
Yes, you heard correctly.
Rarely do I give in to revulsion,
but for the other scum that is
Cioccolata, I make an exception.
I expect he'll reduce Rome
to rubble in his rampage.
You're worried he might go overboard?
That's why I'm counting
on you to intervene.
You must be the one to seize control.
Those two cannot be allowed
to know what Trish knows,
nor can they ever find
out about what Bucciarati
and his band of fools
are looking for in Rome.
You're the only one I'm
able to trust. Got that?
You and you alone are my number one.
I won't let you down. Trust me.
I live only to serve and defend you.
Sorry for hogging the phone like that.
You can have it back now.
Thanks a lot.
Uh, can you hear me?
What the hell did you touch, Mista?
It's crawling all over you!
I know as much as you!
Just focus on finding the damn user!
I can't kick his ass
until you sniff him out!
Lil' bummer!
Not good.
He's already massacred a
bunch of people at this rate.
He's about to mess up the entire village.
He's just indiscriminately
attacking civilians. Damn it.
I can barely tell him apart.
This asshole isn't gonna be easy to find.
What's going on up there?
Report.
Well, there's bubbly shit on my hand and I
have no idea where the hell it came from.
It feels like some weird mold that's
slowly eating away at my skin.
I'm beginning to think that
it's oozing out of my body.?
It's the same crap that
came bursting out of
those other people and
turned them to slime.
I got some bad news.
We won't be able to dock.
There's no way we'll make it up
the stairs to the parking lot.
All we can do is hop back on the
boat and try to get somewhere safe.
Any signs of breathing on shore?
I can't pick up anything.
Hold on, Buterati.
We shouldn't move until we've figured
out exactly what's attacking us.
Who knows what's going to happen?
What's going to happen is we'll get
eaten alive if we keep standing here.
Sorry.
Now the stuff's getting all over me!
It's inside!
Where's the stuff coming from? It's...
Mista!
Here, grab on!
Mista, do not stretch out your hand!
There's a trigger!
This stand relies on a very
specific trigger to attack!
A specific... What now?
What the hell do you mean?
It started acting up the
second I lowered my hand.
Now that I think about it,
the first time it attacked me was
when I reached down to grab my gun.
And it didn't get that drunk guy
until he jumped down the stairs.
The other guy had also
climbed down the stairs,
while the Rancho had to
jump down to the boat!
So moving to a lower location is
what triggers this thing to attack.
But, even so, at this rate,
you guys are all gonna be...
He still won't descend.
I thought he'd board the
boat to save his friend.
Perhaps he figured it out.
My little trick.
Green tea's quirky secret.
This mold.
I've read about it before.
It starts by making a home
inside an insect's body.
When the insect moves to a lower
point, it spreads and kills its host.
It's called Entomophaga greely.
The stand works in the same way,
moving down from a higher
to a lower location.
That's what causes the
mold to act like this.
But this is a stand.
For what reason would it behave this way?
Just think about it for a second.
That's how it gets its range.
It jumps from one body to another,
just like the fungus does.
If the host moves even a little, the
stand's reach will drastically blow up.
That's exactly what its user wants.
And the total behavior of a stand
is a reflection of its user's will.
Narancia, get back on shore!
Climb out of the damn boat now! Mista!
Get your ass over here!
Come on, push!
My foot just broke.
Throw the turtle, Narancia.
Try to aim it at Mista.
Perfect, Narancia.
Yeah, that's good.
Right where I want it.
Both you and the turtle are standing
exactly where I need you to be!
Yee-haw!
Good work, Mista.
As long as we keep moving upwards, we
should ward off any further attacks.
They made it back up.
They all managed to make it to shore,
and there wasn't even one casualty.
Interesting.
I'm eager to know what's next.
They were accusing Not always we were
knowing What is just fiction Or what is
the truth They have a mission They are
the passion But they
dare to tell us What's
bad and what's good Stand up Join us Come
on You'll see this We are the power Cause
there's a future Cause we are the fighters
Just fighting for the right Let's go
Let's go Let's go
Thank you.